Allen D. Place, Jr. papers, Inclusive: 1989-1998, undated Bulk: 1991-1997
Baylor University, Baylor Collections of Political Materials
Allen D. Place, Jr. papers
Inclusive: 1989-1998, undated Bulk: 1991-1997
Baylor University, Baylor Collections of Political Materials http://www.baylor.edu/lib/bcpm/
29
Place, Allen Dwain, Jr., 1955-
84 document boxes
The Allen D. Place, Jr. materials include correspondence, news clippings, legislation, and committee work dated 1991-1998, when Place was a Texas State Representative. Legislation pertains to issues such as criminal jurisprudence, gambling, railroad mergers, and school funding.
Administrative Information
Physical Description
General condition: Good.
Biography/Profile
Allen Dwain Place, Jr. was born on September 22, 1955, in Gatesville, Texas. He graduated from Baylor University with a bachelor's in Business Administration in 1977, and a Juris Doctorate in 1979. Place passed the bar exam that same year and began practicing law in Gatesville.
In a 1990 special election, Place, a Democrat, was selected to replace Bob Melton as the Texas State Representative for the 57th District. From 1990-1992, this district represented Bosque, Coryell, and Hill Counties. Redistricting occurred in 1992 after which Place represented the 59th District, comprised of Comanche, Coryell, Erath, and Hamilton Counties.
Allen Place, Jr. was a member of the 71st-75th Legislatures, from 1990 to 1999. He served on the Criminal Jurisprudence Committee throughout his tenure, fulfilling the role of chair for three terms. Place also sat on the Calendars, Corrections, and Elections Committees, among others. In 1997, he chaired the Senate Bill 97 Select Committee which revised stalking laws in Texas.
Allen D. Place, Jr. is currently an attorney in Gatesville, Texas.
Scope and Content
The Allen D. Place, Jr. papers include correspondence, news clippings, legislation, and committee work dated 1991-1998, when Place was a Texas State Representative.
The Administrative Organizations series includes materials collected by Place while working on legislative issues in Texas. The Agencies subseries includes correspondence, annual reports, memos, and meeting agendas from entities such as the Texas Commission of Alcohol and Drug Abuse, the Texas Department of Health, and the Governor’s office. The Interstate Commerce Commission subseries is primarily composed of documents related to the merger of the Burlington Northern, Inc. and the Atchison, Topeka, and Santa Fe railways.
The Correspondence series is divided into two subseries: Individuals and Subject. The Individuals subseries covers topics such as firearms, education, and the criminal justice system with politicians, educational representatives, and others. The Subject subseries relates directly to topics such as education, school funding, tort reform, and youth issues. Some inmate correspondence is present but has been restricted.
The Legislative Series is divided into four subseries and covers the 72nd-75th Legislatures (1991-1997). The General sub-subseries includes reports, lists, calendars, and policies. Bills are organized numerically and include House Bills, Senate Bills, and other bills formerly considered for legislation. Correspondence houses inquiries about bills under consideration, and the Legislative Clipping Service sub-subseries contains articles from various newspaper outlets used to research topics related to current legislation.
Arrangement
Preliminary inventories for the Allen Place, Jr. papers were created for accessions that took place in 1995 and 1997, and a previous finding aid was completed in 2000.
The current arrangement has restructured this prior finding aid to align items based on Place's legislative terms and includes three series: I. Administrative Organizations, II. Correspondence, and III. Legislative. Each series is further divided into subseries and sub-subseries.
Access Restrictions
All requests for copying of materials must be submitted to the W. R. Poage Legislative Library in writing. Please use the Request Form for Copying Materials sheet. Unpublished materials authored or otherwise produced by the creator (s) of this collection are in the public domain. There are no restrictions on use. Copyright status for other collection materials is unknown. Transmission or reproduction of materials protected by U.S. Copyright Law (Title 17, U.S.C.) beyond that allowed by fair use requires the written permission of the copyright owners. Works not in the public domain cannot be commercially exploited without permission of the copyright owners. Responsibility for any use rests exclusively with the user.
Acquisition Information
Accession No. 29. Acquired 1995-07-06
Related Resources
Related references
“Allen Place” Legislative Reference Library of Texas. Accessed January 18, 2019.
Index Terms
Subjects (Persons)
Place, Allen Dwain, Jr., 1955-
Subjects (Organizations)
Atchison, Topeka, and Santa Fe Railroad Company.; Burlington Northern Inc.; Governor's Task Force on Illegal Gambling in Texas.; Texas. Legislature. House of Representatives. Committee on Criminal Jurisprudence.; Texas. Legislature. House of Representatives.; United States. Interstate Commerce Commission.
Subjects
Alcohol and drug abuse -- Law and legislation -- Texas.; Apportionment (Election law) -- Texas.; Criminal justice.; Criminal law.; Educational law and legislation -- Texas.; EducationDLFinance--Texas.; Firearms--Law and legislation--Texas.; Fraud--Law and legislation--Texas.; Gambling -- Law and legislation -- Texas.; Legislators -- Texas -- Archives.; Railroads--Mergers.
Genres
Agendas (administrative records); Annual reports.; Budgets.; Calendars.; Clippings (Books, newspapers, etc.); Correspondence.; Daily reports.; Legislative bills.; Memorandums.; Photographs.; Records (Documents); Records and briefs.
- Administrative Organizations, 1989-1998; 1
  Administrative Information
  Physical Description
  General condition: Good.
  Biography/Profile
  The Administrative Organizations series is further divided into subseries entitled Agencies, Interstate Commerce Commission, Committee on Criminal Jurisprudence, and Task Force on Illegal Gambling. The materials in this series range from 1989 to 1998.
  The Agencies subseries has inclusive dates of 1989-1998, and consists of correspondence, annual reports, memos, budgets, and meeting agendas. Administrative offices, boards, committees, and departments such as the Texas Commission on Alcohol and Drug Abuse, the Education Coordinating Board, Governor Ann Richards’ office, and the Texas Department of Health are represented. This subseries is arranged in alphabetical order by topic, and the materials are in good condition.
  The Interstate Commerce Commission subseries contains materials from 1995 to 1996, and primarily relates to details of the merger of the Burlington Northern, Inc. and Atchison, Topeka, and Santa Fe railways. Requests and interrogatories, briefs, motions, commentaries, petitions, and notices are present from AMTRAK, power and electric companies, state agencies, natural resource agencies, and other railroads. This subseries is arranged in alphabetical order, and the materials are in good condition.
  The subseries Committee on Criminal Jurisprudence is dated 1994-1997. Contents include House Bills pertaining to firearms, bail bonds, controlled substances, and fraud as well as meeting agendas from the Committee on Criminal Jurisprudence and the Elections Committee. This subseries is organized by chronological order and is in good condition.
  The Task Force on Illegal Gambling subseries consists of materials from 1997. General information gathered by the Task Force concerning gambling laws in other states is included as well as general articles on gambling at the national level. This subseries is arranged in alphabetical order and is in good condition.
  - Agencies, 1989-1998; 1
    - Agriculture, 1991-1994 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Texas Commission on Alcohol and Drug Abuse, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Texas Commission on Alcohol and Drug Abuse, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Texas Commission on Alcohol and Drug Abuse, 1991-1993 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Attorney General, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Attorney General, 1991-1993 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Auditor, 1992-1993 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Bar of Texas, 1991-1992 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Bar of Texas, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Bond Review Board, 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Department of Commerce, 1990-1994 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Department of Commerce, 1991-1998 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Department of Commerce, 1992-1994 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Comptroller, 1991-1994 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Education Agency, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Education Agency, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Education Agency, 1990-1994 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Education Agency, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Education Coordinating Board, 1990-1991 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Employment Commission, 1990-1992 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Employment Commission, 1991-1992 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - General Service Commission, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - General Service Commission, 1992-1994 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Governor Ann Richards, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Governor Ann Richards, 1991-1992 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Governor Ann Richards, 1991-1994 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Governor Ann Richards, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Texas Department of Health, 1989-1992 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Texas Department of Health, 1991-1994 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Highways and Public Transportation: State Department, 1990-1993 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Human Services, 1990-1991 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Human Services, 1991-1993 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Insurance, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Insurance, 1992-1994 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Insurance, State Board, 1991-1992 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Inter-Agency Memos, 1991-1992 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Inter-Office Memos, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Inter-Office Memos, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Joint Select Committee on Jury Handbook (1 of 5), 1993 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Joint Select Committee on Jury Handbook (2 of 5), 1993 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Joint Select Committee on Jury Handbook (3 of 5), 1993 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Joint Select Committee on Jury Handbook (4 of 5), 1993 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Joint Select Committee on Jury Handbook (5 of 5), 1993 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - House Select Committee on Rules, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Rules Group, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Office of the Speaker, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Office of the Speaker, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Texas Punishment Standard Commission (1 of 2), 1992 January 10 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Texas Punishment Standard Commission (2 of 2), 1992 January 10 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Texas Punishment Standard Commission, 1992 April 3 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Texas Punishment Standard Commission, 1992 May 12 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Texas Punishment Standard Commission, 1992 July 24 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Texas Punishment Standard Commission, 1992 August 28 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Texas Punishment Standard Commission, 1992 October 2 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Texas Punishment Standard Commission, 1992 November 20 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Texas Punishment Standard Commission, 1992 December 11 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Washington Model for Civil Commitment, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Interstate Commerce Commission, 1994-1997; 2
    - Administrative Law Judge, 1995 May 10 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Allied Rail Unions, 1995 June (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - American Public Power Transportation, 1995 June 9 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - AMTRAK, 1995 May (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - AMTRAK, 1995 June (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Arizona Electric Power Cooperative, 1995 March-October (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Arizona Public Service Company, 1995 May-June (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Arndt, Richard A., 1995 May 9 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - ASARCO, 1995 May 9 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Atchison, Topeka and Santa Fe, 1995 May 9 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Atchison, Topeka and Santa Fe, 1995 December 19 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Banks, Robert L., 1995 June 19 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Birmingham Southern Railroad, 1995 May 5 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Brotherhood of Locomotive Engineers, 1995 May-June (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Bunge Corporation, 1995 May-June (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Burlington Northern, Incorporated and Santa Fe Pacific Corporation, 1995 June 29 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Burlington Northern, Incorporated and Santa Fe Pacific Corporation, 1994 May 4 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Burlington Northern, Incorporated and Santa Fe Pacific Corporation, Responses Volume 1 (1 of 4), 1995 June 9 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Burlington Northern, Incorporated and Santa Fe Pacific Corporation, Responses Volume 1 (2 of 4 ), 1995 June 9 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Burlington Northern, Incorporated and Santa Fe Pacific Corporation Responses Volume 1 (3 of 4), 1995 June 9 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Burlington Northern, Incorporated and Santa Fe Pacific Corporation Responses Volume 1 (4 of 4), 1995 June 9 (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Burlington Northern, Incorporated and Santa Fe Pacific Corporation, Responses Volume 2 (1 of 3), 1995 June 9 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Burlington Northern, Incorporated and Santa Fe Pacific Corporation, Responses Volume 2 (2 of 3), 1995 June 9 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Burlington Northern, Incorporated and Santa Fe Pacific Corporation, Responses Volume 2 (3 of 3), 1995 June 9 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Burlington Northern, Incorporated and Santa Fe Pacific Corporation, Responses Volume 3 (1 of 4), 1995 June 9 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Burlington Northern, Incorporated and Santa Fe Pacific Corporation, Responses Volume 3 (2 of 4), 1995 June 9 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Burlington Northern, Incorporated and Santa Fe Pacific Corporation, Responses Volume 3 (3 of 4), 1995 June 9 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Burlington Northern, Incorporated and Santa Fe Pacific Corporation, Responses Volume 3 (4 of 4), 1995 June 9 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - California Attorney General, 1995 June 7 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Cargill, Incorporated, 1995 May 8 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Cen-Tex Rail Link, Ltd., 1995 April 18 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Cen-Tex Rail Link and South Orient, 1995 May-June (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Central Power and Light, 1995 May-June (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Chaco Energy Company, 1995 May-June (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Conrail, Incorporated, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Cook, John R. [Texas Representative], 1995 November 29 (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Duluth Missabe and Iron Range, 1995 May 5 (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - Elgin, Joliet and Eastern, 1995 May 5 (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - Farmrail Corporation and Grainbelt, 1995 January-May (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - Farmrail Corporation and Grainbelt, 1995 June-July (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Farmrail Corporation, 1995 May-September (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Fitzgerald, John D., 1995 September 14 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Grainbelt Corporation, 1995 May-September (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Houston Lighting and Power, 1995 March-May (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Houston Lighting and Power, 1995 June-October (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Illinois Central Railroad, 1995 April-May (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Illinois Central Railroad, 1995 June (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Illinois Department of Transportation, 1995 May 10 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, 1995 April-May (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Junell, Robert [Representative], 1995 November 8 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Kansas City Southern, 1995 February-December (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Kansas Shippers Association, 1995 May 8 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Keokuk Junction Railway, 1995 April-May (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Keokuk Junction Railway, 1995 June-July (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - L.E. Peabody and Associates, 1995 May 17 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Louis Dreyfus Corporation, 1995 May 1 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Minnesota Department of Transportation, 1995 May 9 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Montana Wheat and Barley Committee, 1995 June 21 (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - National Industrial Transportation, 1995 May-June (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - National Railroad Passenger Corporation, 1995 June 19 (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - Notice of Consummation, 1995 October 5 (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - Offerle Co-operative Grain and Supply, 1995 March 13 (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - Oklahoma Department of Transportation, 1995 June-September (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - Oklahoma Gas and Electric, 1995 March-September (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - Oral Argument Requests, 1995 June 26 (Box 10, Folder 19)
    - Oregon Department of Transportation and PUC, 1995 May 10 (Box 10, Folder 20)
    - Owens-Corning Fiberglass, 1995 May 8 (Box 10, Folder 21)
    - Phillips Petroleum, 1995-1996 January-September (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Place, Allen D., Jr., 1995 April-May (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Port of Corpus Christi Authority, 1995 June 5 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Port of Tacoma and Port of Seattle, 1995 May 29 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Public Utility Commission of Texas, 1995 May 18 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Railroad Commission of Texas, 1995 December 21 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Rebuttal Testimony, 1995 June 21 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Requests for Conditions and Comments, 1995 May 30 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Seagraves, Whiteface and Lubbock Railroad, 1995 April- June (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Settlement Agreements, 1995 May 11 (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Society of the Plastic Industry, 1995 May-June (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Southern Orient Railroad, 1995 April-May (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Southern California Regional Rail Authority, 1995 March-June (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Southwestern Public Service and Tuco (1 of 3), 1995 May-October (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - Southwestern Public Service and Tuco (2 of 3), 1995 June 19 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Southwestern Public Service and Tuco (3 of 3), 1995 May-June (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Statement, 1995 June 14 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Supporters of the Merger (1 of 3), 1995 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Supporters of the Merger (2 of 3), 1995 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Supporters of the Merger (3 of 3), 1995 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Texas Attorney General, 1996 January 11 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Texas Department of Transportation, 1995 May 9 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Texas House of Representatives, 1996 March (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Texas Office of Public Utility Counsel, 1995 May 10 (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Toledo, Peoria & Western Railway, 1995 June-July (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Transportation Communication Union, 1995 May 9 (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - Tuco, Incorporated, 1995 May 17 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Tucson Electric Power Company, 1995 May-June (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Union Pacific Corporation, 1995-1996 March-June (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - United States Department of Agriculture, 1995 May 10 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - United States Department of Justice, 1995 May-June (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - United States Department of Transportation, 1995 May-June (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - United Transportation Union, 1995 April-November (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Universal Forest Product, 1995 May (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Washington State, 1995 May 9 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Western Coal Traffic League, 1995 May-October (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Western Fuels Association, Incorporated and Sunflower Electric Power, 1995 May 8 (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Western Fuels Association, 1995 May-June (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - Western Fuels Service, 1995 June 29 (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - Western Resources, 1995 May-September (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - Worsham, Forsythe and Wooldridge, 1995 May 26 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Interstate Commerce Commission Decisions, 1995 April-May (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Interstate Commerce Commission Decisions (1 of 2), 1995 June (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Interstate Commerce Commission Decisions (2 of 2), 1995 June (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Interstate Commerce Commission Decisions, 1995 February-December (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Committee on Criminal Jurisprudence, 1994-1997; 3
    - Agenda, Subcommittee on Laws and Procedures Relating to Death Sentences, 1994 June 1 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Death Sentence, 1994 June 1 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Habeas Review, 1994 September 9 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - HB 278, Searches of Students and Children, 1997 (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - HB 908, Appointment of Defendant Counsel in a Criminal Case, 1997 (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - HB 1185, Fraud, 1997 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - HB 1194, Bail and Bonds, 1997 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - HB 1650, Commercial Real Estate Broker’s Lien, 1997 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - HB 2634, Administrative Fees Collected by Community Supervision and Corrections Departments, 1997 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - HB 2635, Operation of State Jail Felony, 1997 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - HB 2826, Qualifications of Supervision and Corrections Officers, 1997 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - HB 2827, Death of an Inmate, 1997 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - HB 2828, Public Access of Personal Information, 1997 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - HB 2831, Procedures and Standards Governing Release on Personal Bond, 1997 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Memos, 1997 (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - Parole, 1997 (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - HB 441, Controlled Substance, 1997 January 14 (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - HB 660, Possession of Certain Firearms by a Minor, 1997 January 23 (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - HB 661, Transfer of Certain Firearms, 1997 January 23 (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - HB 662, Deadly Conduct Involving a Firearm, 1997 January 23 (Box 15, Folder 15)
    - HB 747, Youth Drug Programs, 1997 January 27 (Box 15, Folder 16)
    - HB 2559, Possession of Drugs with an Intent to Deliver, 1997 March 27 (Box 15, Folder 17)
    - Elections Committee Meeting, 1997 February 25 (Box 15, Folder 18)
    - Elections Committee Meeting, 1997 March 4 (Box 15, Folder 19)
    - Elections Committee Meeting, 1997 March 25 (Box 15, Folder 20)
    - Elections Committee Meeting, 1997 April 1 (Box 15, Folder 21)
    - Elections Committee Meeting, 1997 April 8 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Meeting Agenda, 1997 February 19 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Meeting Agenda, 1997 February 26 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Meeting Agenda, 1997 March 5 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Meeting Agenda, 1997 March 12 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Meeting Agenda, 1997 March 19 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Meeting Agenda, 1997 March 26 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Meeting Agenda, 1997 April 2 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Meeting Agenda, 1997 April 9 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Meeting Agenda, 1997 April 16 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Meeting Agenda, 1997 April 23 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Meeting Agenda, 1997 May 1 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Meeting Agenda, 1997 May 15 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Task Force on Illegal Gambling, 1997; 4
    - Alabama, 1997 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Alaska, 1997 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Arkansas, 1997 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Arizona, 1997 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Articles on Gambling, General, 1997 (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - California, 1997 (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Colorado, 1997 (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Connecticut, 1997 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Criminal Jurisprudence, 1997 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Delaware, 1997 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Florida, 1997 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Georgia, 1997 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Hawaii, 1997 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Idaho, 1997 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Illinois, 1997 (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Indiana, 1997 (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - Iowa, 1997 (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - Kansas, 1997 (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - Kentucky, 1997 (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - Louisiana, 1997 (Box 19, Folder 13)
    - Maine, 1997 (Box 19, Folder 14)
    - Massachusetts, 1997 (Box 19, Folder 15)
    - Michigan, 1997 (Box 19, Folder 16)
    - Minnesota, 1997 (Box 19, Folder 17)
    - Mississippi, 1997 (Box 19, Folder 18)
    - Missouri, 1997 (Box 19, Folder 19)
    - Montana, 1997 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Nebraska, 1997 (Box 20, Folder 2)